hi Springs and in this installment of
嗨，斯普林斯，在本期的
spring test we're going to go ahead and
春季测试，我们将继续前进，
look at distributed tracing we're going
看看我们要进行的分布式跟踪
to do so in terms of the open system
就开放系统而言
project this to be tracing in theory is
预计这在理论上是可追溯的
very simple what we want to do is to
非常简单，我们要做的是
correlate the quest from one service to
将一项服务的任务与
another so as a message arrives at one
另一则消息到达
node and then proceeds to another end to
节点，然后转到另一端
another and to another we want to go to
一个又一个我们想去
mark in time somewhere that that message
在该消息的某处及时标记
has been received and it's been
已经收到，已经
perpetuated on down the line this sounds
听起来永远如此
like it could be fairly simple right in
就像它可能很简单
serious times very simple but then I
严重的时候很简单，但后来我
turned out to be quite a bear some
原来是一些熊
people have attempted to solve this in
人们试图解决这个问题
terms of logging right you have a unique
拥有正确记录权的条款
identifier that gets perpetuate along
永存的标识符
with every message or every request that
每个消息或每个请求
unique identifier is a is a trace ID and
唯一标识符是a是跟踪ID，
as long as you log that out you can then
只要您注销就可以
sort of sift through the logs later on
稍后在日志中进行某种筛选
and sort of ascertain where the message
并确定消息在哪里
has arrived or what it messages been in
已经到达或消息内容
the course of its progression through
其发展历程
the system that certainly has some
肯定有一些系统
benefits and that works to a point of
好处，并达到一定程度
course in order to make that work you
当然是为了使你工作
have to trap everywhere every possible
必须千方百计地陷井
conceivable place in the system where a
在系统中可以想到的地方
message may exit and enter into the
消息可能会退出并进入
system and be sure to add logic to
系统，并确保向其中添加逻辑
either recognize a message that already
要么识别已经存在的消息
has a crazed ID or if it's absent a
带有疯狂的ID，或者缺少
trace ID to then give it a trace ID and
跟踪ID，然后为其提供跟踪ID，并
then be sure to perpetuate that down the
然后确保将其永久保留下来
chain so for all the types of requests
链，因此对于所有类型的请求
into the system being over HTTP or HTTPS
通过HTTP或HTTPS进入系统
or after reactive and asynchronous or if
或反应式和异步后，或者
they're synchronous if their messaging
他们是同步的，如果他们的消息
centric or Patrick Osterman queue or
中心或Patrick Osterman队列或
whatever everywhere you have message
随处可见
that moves to the system you need to go
移到您需要去的系统上
to a fix an ID and perpetuated in a
修复ID，并在其中永久保留
consistent way add to that extra
一致的方式增加了额外的费用
dimension that in some cases you have
在某些情况下具有的尺寸
different languages different you know
你知道的不同语言
different platforms the dimensions of of
不同平台的尺寸
complexity become overwhelming after a
复杂性变得压倒性
point right so what we're going to talk
指出正确，所以我们要谈什么
about today is an abstraction inside of
今天大概是
spring type called spring cloud salute
春季型称为春云敬礼
Google
谷歌
please of course you know in English it
当然请用英语知道
describes somebody who's a a detective
描述某人是侦探
somebody who finds
有人发现
right so sooth is a generic attraction
对，舒缓是一个普遍的吸引力
it has as heart the concept of a trace a
它具有痕迹的概念
trace describes the aggregate journey
跟踪描述了整个旅程
from A to Z or a bit of a message in a
从A到Z或
system as messages proceed from one note
消息从一个音符处继续时的系统
to another they create new spans so if
到另一个他们创建新的跨度，所以如果
you have one message that goes through
你有一条消息通过
four four nodes they'll have a
四个四个节点，他们将有一个
corresponding number of spans maybe four
对应的跨度可能是四个
spans and one trace per all four of
跨度和所有四个中的一个痕迹
those pants right so you'll have one
那条裤子对，所以你会有一条
trace and multiple spans for any given
任何给定的跟踪和多个跨度
request and that's the basic domain
请求，这是基本域
model now this Amin model this sort of
现在模拟这个阿敏模拟这样的
view of the of the world of tracing is
跟踪世界的观点是
so because that's actually the
所以因为这实际上是
underpinning of an attempt to
尝试的基础
standardize not necessarily the API but
标准化不一定是API，而是
the language and the concepts of
语言和概念
distributed tracing that's called the
分布式跟踪，称为
open tracing initiative now open tracing
公开跟踪计划现在公开跟踪
has it was started by one of the folks
它是由一个人开始的吗
who work on the Google dapper paper
在Google精简版纸上工作的人
which is a originator if you know sort
如果您知道排序的话，那是发起者
of the granddaddy of should be tracing
的祖父应该追踪
as we know it's a and on which Zipkin
我们知道这是Zipkin
itself is based right so this is a this
本身是基于权利的，所以这是一个
is an ideal right we're hoping to get
是我们希望得到的理想权利
here we're hoping Natalie vendor-neutral
在这里，我们希望Natalie与供应商无关
open standard for distributed phasing
分布式调相的开放标准
right now in practice this doesn't quite
现在在实践中还不完全
work as it should right you can't you
应该工作就可以了
can't take a open tracing implementation
无法采用公开跟踪实施
adage application and have it produce
格言应用并产生
uniform traces consistently across
一致的痕迹贯穿
different languages Lipkin under the end
不同语言的Lipkin底下
does for some of the implementations are
对某些实现所做的是
already feature that right so remember
已经具有正确的功能，所以请记住
Zipkin itself is a service data base
Zipkin本身是服务数据库
it's a database that's meant to store
这是一个要存储的数据库
trace information
跟踪信息
so there are different clients for
所以有不同的客户
existence what we're going to talk about
存在我们将要谈论的
today is the clients that the
今天是客户
implementation that shifts the spring
改变春天的实现
clouds flute as implementation of spring
云长笛作为春天的实施
constants in theory you could plug in
理论上可以插入的常量
others but there's this core FBI
其他人，但是有这个核心的联邦调查局
of which one is a are that can support
其中一个是可以支持的
okay so in order to make this work we're
好的，为了完成这项工作，我们
going to need a different server okay
需要一个不同的服务器好吗
says if in service we want to actually
说如果我们在服务中
have the API itself and a user interface
具有API本身和用户界面
and so we're going to add both for that
因此，我们将为此添加两者
it'll generate then we're going built-in
它会生成，然后我们将内置
client just will just have the web
客户只会拥有网络
support and the different client support
支持和不同的客户支持
we'll get ready to serve a bit to don't
我们将准备好服务一点
need that let up easy user interface all
需要让所有轻松的用户界面
right
对
and we'll have a service whatever that
无论如何我们都会提供服务
was a bit scary though Jerry and open up
虽然杰里和开放有点害怕
this client here open up through the
这个客户在这里通过
conservator okay open
储藏柜可以打开
so let's get the system server up and
因此，让我们启动系统服务器，
running first the first thing we need to
首先运行我们需要做的第一件事
do is specify a few properties we want
要做的就是指定一些我们想要的属性
this thing to run import 94 11 now
这个东西现在要运行导入94 11
Lipkin is an API there are several
Lipkin是一个API，有几种
different ways you can you can talk to
您可以与之交谈的不同方式
the API the most arrest of course is
API最引人注目的当然是
just use rest and that's what we learn
只是利用休息，这就是我们学到的东西
during a good one
在一个好人中
you could also asynchronously deliver
您也可以异步交付
messages to a listen feed server and I
消息发送到侦听供稿服务器，我
could have elected back on the exponent
本来可以重选指数
issue Iser to add a module that
发出Iser添加一个模块
supported accepting swing cloud screen
支持接受摇摆云屏幕
courage or marshals other methods might
勇气或法警其他方法可能
span information over messages delivered
将信息跨过已传递的消息
using inexpensive screen binder to
使用廉价的屏幕粘合剂
advise mq of that you fought for or
告知mq您为之奋斗或
whatever time so we're gonna run this
不管什么时候，我们要运行这个
important set 94 Levin that's a common
重要的一组94莱文很常见
default for the skinnin if you have that
如果有的话，默认为skinnin
and you don't have to tell the client on
而且您不必告诉客户
which you know via the services on this
您通过此服务知道的
and then we need to actually activate
然后我们需要实际激活
there's a game server now you may have
现在可能有一个游戏服务器
noticed that this is not a spring cloud
注意到这不是春天的云
adaptation this is actually the
适应这实际上是
different duck server package in the iOS
iOS中的其他鸭子服务器包
App Engine Java module the more
App Engine Java模块越多
consistent private sites see the Dukan
一致的私人网站，请参阅杜坎
server itself is built in the delivery
服务器本身内置在交付中
using spring boots so it's actually the
使用 spring boot ，所以实际上
open zip in project is it is a teaching
在项目中打开zip是教学
that can do say Stasiak
可以说斯塔西亚克
and last code but should be very
最后的代码，但应该非常
familiar to images used in Buddhist can
熟悉佛教罐中使用的图像
tabs on what's going on here we have a
在这里发生了什么事，我们有一个
zip ensure we have that between it's
zip确保我们之间有
going to start up on 494 level and now
将从494级开始，现在
it's supposed to build a client and a
它应该建立一个客户和一个
service so let's see what we have here
服务，让我们看看这里有什么
we have the client also the finest if
我们也有最好的客户
you can please all lecture about itself
你可以请所有关于自己的演讲
yourself well we started
你好，我们开始了
this is it at all
就是这样
other okay but our client we're gonna
其他还可以，但我们的客户要
have a simple endpoint and we'll just
有一个简单的端点，我们将
trigger a call to another node so here
触发到另一个节点的呼叫，所以这里
you go call something get mapping by
你去打电话找东西
string slide and we're going to call
弦滑，我们要打电话
another surface using a restaurant so
使用餐厅的另一面
I'm going to define a beam of cyber
我要定义一束网络
Olympics remember the rest template is a
奥运会请记住，其余模板是
as a sort of theme in the application of
作为应用中的一种主题
sections it's a component that will send
部分是将发送的组件
messages and requests to other nodes so
消息和其他节点的请求
we need to give screen cloud sleep a
我们需要让屏幕云进入睡眠状态
chance to intercept requests that have
机会拦截具有以下内容的请求
been made from the justify so in swing
是从辩解中取得的，所以摇摆不定
Constance here's your scene and looking
康斯坦斯，这是你的情景
figure intercepts for us to
图为我们截取
automatically trace the messages were
自动跟踪邮件
like a made a necklace compass so make
像制作的项链指南针一样
sure you configure it as a beam that the
确保将其配置为光束
force meeting in excess of private sales
超过私人销售的强制会议
variable as a minute that other extinct
一分钟可变的其他灭绝
else will be able to see that scene it
否则就能看到那个场景了
won't know to concede it for you
不会为你让步
so this set of center some good French
所以这套中心有些不错的法国菜
teen going to call HTTP low go home give
青少年要打电话给HTTP低回家
me one
我一个
hi okay I'm just going to get the data
嗨，好吧，我只是要获取数据
back and you want to see body well this
回来，你想看身体很好
is a very simple example again I could
再次是一个非常简单的例子
Mississippi easier if I were using us
如果我使用我们，密西西比州会更容易
the same time discovery time I had this
在同一时间发现我
had that's plug in to talk to us or
插入了与我们交谈的信息或
something like that so for now it's just
这样的事情，所以现在
it's advices to know we're going to call
建议我们打电话给我们
another node of course see dat one
当然，另一个节点
that's going to be our service
这将是我们的服务
implementation will originate the nodes
实现将发起节点
here on the client is sprinkles people
在客户端上这是洒人
know that this is a client because we're
知道这是一个客户，因为我们
going to give it a name this is the same
要给它起个名字是一样的
name that these four Service
命名这四个服务
registration discovered and you can keep
发现注册，您可以保留
that off now let's go ahead and since it
现在，让我们继续，因为它
that's service implementation of service
那就是服务的服务实现
application a rest controller okay we'll
应用 rest controller 好吧，我们将
say at kidnapping my
说绑架我的
same five return hello
同样五个回声你好
so those are our Oh ever so
所以这些都是我们的哦
sophisticated a service implementation
完善的服务实现
will run this on port 8081 almost like
将在端口8081上运行，就像
this Amin so okay make it easier than
这个阿敏好吧，比
the sound of happen to run this now our
碰巧的声音现在就运行了
client this is the pipe it should be up
客户端，这是管道，应该向上
and running down 1480 and local host
并运行1480和本地主机
8080 i
8080我
Oh
哦
basic service implementation on the city
城市基本服务实施
81 so for all offenses it's ready take
81因此，对于所有违法行为，一切准备就绪
off a request
取消请求
Oh localhost:8080 one let's keep it up
哦localhost：8080让我们继续
sir still spinning up
先生还在旋转
there we go the service is just setting
我们去那里的服务只是设置
up now it's working so we have now a
现在它正在工作，所以我们现在有一个
request that has gone from 8080 all
从8080所有的请求
those to 1881 and in fact we can see the
那些到1881年，实际上我们可以看到
results confirmed here let's see what
结果确认在这里，让我们看看
the server that we spun up have to say
我们启动的服务器必须说
about that now the different server is
关于这一点，现在不同的服务器是
running on port 94 11 you can see that
在端口94 11上运行，您可以看到
is where your folks folks notice the
是您的乡亲注意到的地方
clients on the service if you click on
客户，如果您单击
service for example you can see the
例如服务，您可以看到
particular endpoints all the particular
特定端点，所有特定端点
interests in English books click once in
对英语书籍的兴趣单击一次
them in that particular nodes we can
他们在那个特定的节点，我们可以
sail and see all requests pertaining to
航行并查看与以下内容有关的所有请求
the high influence and fine print and
高影响力和精美的印刷品，
show that they're made with your quest
证明他们是您追求的
that has a couple of spins and we can
有几个旋转，我们可以
see here that the request originated as
在这里看到请求源自
a defiant at the going to the HTTP high
抵制HTTP高涨
info and then maybe five milliseconds on
信息，然后大概五毫秒
fire or maybe a five milliseconds later
起火或大约五毫秒后
it goes to the service where it's going
它去了要去的地方
to be sufficiently high in point on that
在这一点上足够高
node and listen to the waterfall graph
节点并收听瀑布图
here again if you had ten different
如果你有十种不同的话再来一次
requests you see how much more
要求您查看更多
interesting for graph of the of the
有趣的
ecosystem stand for that message across
生态系统代表着这一信息
to the keynote we can click on each one
在主题演讲中，我们可以单击每个主题
of these and we get some interesting
这些中，我们得到一些有趣的东西
information this information down here
在此提供此信息
all this is a physical tag and the tags
所有这些都是物理标签
give you extra metadata extra context
给您额外的元数据额外的上下文
about the request itself here we can see
关于请求本身，我们可以在这里看到
that as an issue be request because it
作为一个问题被要求，因为它
should be a verb use the host system as
应该是动词使用宿主系统作为
address or if you know but then and if
地址，或者如果您知道，但是然后，如果
we have it may give you things Pacific
我们有可能给你太平洋的东西
information and you can submit and
信息，您可以提交和
capture custom tags as well right so you
也可以捕获自定义标签，所以您
can inject a a span using screen size
可以使用屏幕尺寸注入跨度
food because capture custom tags as well
食物，因为也可以捕获自定义标签
you can use this facility to add things
您可以使用此功能添加东西
that you can use the correlate is a
您可以使用相关系数的是
request you know over HTTP for example -
通过HTTP请求您知道-
in business transaction maybe sinhala
在商业交易中可能是sinhala
space or Verizon or via you know the
空间或Verizon或通过您知道
customer ID or whatever you want but
客户ID或您想要的任何东西
make no mistake this is not about
没错，这不是关于
warehousing we're not going to use this
仓库，我们将不使用此
information to understand what skims it
信息，以了解它是什么
on the website five years ago this is
在五年前的网站上，这是
all about online 70 so most
关于在线70的所有内容
organizations don't keep most you know
组织不会让您知道最多
they don't keep all their good and if
他们没有保持自己的全部利益，如果
they do they don't keep it some more
他们这样做，他们不保留更多
than
比
a certain sort of window window the
某种窗户
amount of pot might have a small amount
锅里可能有少量
of time during which they can keep it
他们可以保留的时间
and analyze it if they need to and in
并分析是否需要
the exercise that they archive it off it
他们将其存档的练习
just go away
刚刚离开
you're not going to use this for for
您不会将其用于
what else this is all about online
还有什么关于在线的
parameters but in that regard it's very
参数，但是在这方面
useful a lot of teams don't know what
很多团队都不知道有用
they're like granularity is fine so
他们就像粒度很好，所以
spring cloud flute butter false I think
春云笛黄油假我想
um doesn't it keeps just a small subset
嗯，不是只有一小部分
of the requests I think it was that
我认为的要求是
percentages but you can change that you
百分比，但您可以更改
can change how many requests are
可以更改请求数
retained by changing the
通过更改保留
there's no temper percentage so the
没有脾气百分比，所以
default sample percentage is one out of
默认样本百分比是十分之一
a ten requests with point one you can
与第一点的十个请求，您可以
change that by making it so not one size
通过使其不成为一种尺寸来改变它
that weighs everybody 100% this is a
每个人的体重为100％
property and if you have this property
财产，如果你有这个财产
on both sides and both sides or
在两侧和两侧或
automatically record every single
自动记录每一个
message there's no hope with core Jones
信息，琼斯核心没有希望
or register your own custom sampler team
或注册自己的自定义采样器团队
myself sampler is the callback interface
我自己的采样器是回调接口
include them because they return new
包括它们，因为它们返回新的
always sampler for example and that give
例如总是采样器
you a sum of those as a sample every
您每个样本的总和
single request let's observe December
单个请求让我们来观察十二月
contract is very simple it just examples
合同很简单，只是例子
given us back please
请给我们回来
you can return yet familiar in a
您可以返回但熟悉的
basement office and arbiters in closely
地下室与仲裁员紧密联系
us this is mercury and yesterday for
我们这是汞，昨天
example what everyone alright so this
例子，每个人都还好，所以这
has been a very simple look at them
看起来很简单
spring plug to remember that this
弹簧塞要记住这一点
abstraction is there under spring clouds
春天的云层下有抽象
so in most cases you can add the SIM
因此在大多数情况下，您可以添加SIM卡
card started if can dependency at your
卡可以启动，如果可以依赖您
Fastpass
快速通道
stand up as if in server on the side and
站起来就像在服务器旁边
all of the things that you do when your
当你做的所有事情
students and the physical spring cloud
学生和物理春天的云
applications get over a Tchaikovsky lab
应用程序超越了柴可夫斯基实验室
and to or you know anything over screen
和或您知道屏幕上的任何内容
touchscreen or anything to do with rest
触摸屏或与休息有关的任何事情
or this little micro flexi or the obtain
或这个小的柔韧性或获得
rest client or the rel template all
其余客户端或rel模板全部
these all these sort of ingress and you
这些所有这些入口，你
get points in the application in central
在中央应用程序中获得积分
Spain types of applications are
西班牙的申请类型是
automatically instrumented for you and
自动为您检测
they were all honor and observers and
他们都是荣誉和观察员，
copies or the samplers that you can
您可以复制或采样
configure and so the server itself you
配置，因此服务器本身
know I've just stood up a very simple
知道我刚刚站起来很简单
API and this stateless right now the
API和现在的无状态
data is just stored in memory which is
数据只是存储在内存中
you know simple enough for a demo but
您知道足够简单的演示，但
you can also configure data source and
您还可以配置数据源和
point it to for example to my sequel so
指向它例如我的续集
this is very common option as well
这也是非常常见的选择
there's work being done to make
有工作要做
elasticsearch and other Institute's
elasticsearch和其他研究所的
story for certificate itself so okay
证书本身的故事很好
with all that thanks for tuning in
非常感谢您收看
invest a few next
下一步再投资